The Government’s sugar tax on soft drinks has brought in half as much money as Ministers first predicted it would generate, the first official data on the policy has shown.
首批关于这项政策的官方数据显示，政府对软饮料征收的糖税带来的收入只有大臣们最初预测的一半。
First announced in March 2016, the tax, which applies to soft drinks containing more than 5g of sugar per 100ml, was introduced to help reduce childhood obesity.
这项税于2016年3月首次宣布，适用于每100毫升含糖量超过5克的软饮料，其出台是为了帮助减少儿童肥胖。
It is believed that today’s children and teenagers are consuming three times the recommended level of sugar, putting them at a higher risk of the disease.
据信，如今的儿童和青少年摄入的糖是推荐量的三倍，这使他们患上这种疾病的风险更高。
Initially the sugar tax was expected to make £520m a year for the Treasury.
最初，糖税预计每年能为财政部带来5.2亿英镑收入。
However, data from the first six months showed it would make less than half this amount.
然而，前六个月的数据显示，糖税的收入将不到这一数额的一半。
At present it is expected to generate £240m for the year ending in April 2019, which will go to school sports.
目前，预计在截至2019年4月的这一年里，糖税将带来2.4亿英镑收入，这笔钱将用于学校体育。
It comes after more than half of soft drinks sold in shops have had their sugar levels cut by manufacturers so they can avoid paying the tax.
此前，为了避免缴纳这项税，制造商已经降低了商店在售软饮料中一半以上产品的含糖量。
Drinks now contain 45 million fewer kilos of sugar as a result of manufacturers’ efforts to avoid the charge, according to Treasury figures.
根据财政部的数据，由于制造商努力规避这项税费，如今饮料中的糖减少了4500万千克。
Since April, drinks companies have been forced to pay between 18p and 24p for every litre of sugary drink they produce or import, depending on the sugar content.
自4月以来，饮料公司被迫为其生产或进口的每升含糖饮料缴纳18至24便士，具体金额取决于含糖量。
However, some high-sugar brands, like Classic Coca-Cola, have accepted the sugar tax and are refusing to change for fear of upsetting consumers.
然而，经典可口可乐等一些高糖品牌已经接受了糖税，并且唯恐惹得消费者不满而拒绝做出改变。
Fruit juices, milk-based drinks and most alcoholic drinks are free of the tax, as are small companies manufacturing less than 1m litres per year.
果汁、奶基饮料和大多数含酒精饮料都免征这项税，每年生产不足100万升饮料的小公司也是如此。
Today’s figures, according to one government official, show the positive influence the sugar tax is having by raising millions of pounds for sports facilities and healthier eating in schools.
据一位政府官员称，今天公布的数据表明，糖税正在产生积极影响，为学校的体育设施和更健康的饮食筹集了数百万英镑。
Helping the next generation to have a healthy and active childhood is of great importance, and the industry is playing its part.
帮助下一代度过健康而充满活力的童年非常重要，而饮料行业也在尽自己的一份力。